## Pitchayut Chitsinpchayakun

Senior Software Engineer

Address: 55 M.1 Laksam Banphaeo Samutsakhon 74120 Phone: 0819269995

**Email:** pitchayut.jr@gmail.com **Github:** github.com/svnnynior

## **Personal Summary**

I am a Software Engineer with 6+ years of experience working in a tech industry, and has been working in multiple roles during the years, such as, Full-stack Web Developer, Mobile Developer (React Native), SRE/Platform Engineer, Machine Learning Engineer and Data Engineer.

I have a strong passion in building interactive applications and arts with 3D elements or other immersive technologies.

## **Work Experience**

**Senior Software Developer Consultant,** Thoughtworks (Bangkok, Thailand) January 2020 - September 2024

Responsible for delivering quality software and also improving ways of working for clients from all across the world.

- Worked together with an autonomous vehicles company as a Platform Engineer in an SRE team to create a a self-serving Kubernetes platform which helped engineers within the organisation develop their workflows with ease. The platform was used by multiple teams across the company and helped increase the organisation's DORA metrics level from 'Low' to 'High'.
- Maintained and developed four legacy mobile applications from one React Native codebase for a global job-seeking company which allows users from more than six countries to find available job posts. The applications were greatly improved after our team had established a quality strategy and a monitoring system.
- Created an administrative website with React and Express.js which helped a government ran a nationwide campaign which supported millions of users.
- Built a data product bootstrapping tool which reduced the time each team needed to create a data product from months to days. The data product supports data ingestion with Beam and Fivetran, data transformation with Spark and dbt, and are orchestrated using Airflow.
- Involved in a discovery and inception process to craft the right solution for the school evaluation
  process which would be used across Thailand, and built the system by creating an automated
  pipeline starting from congesting survey results to showing the data on a visualisation tool by
  integrating multiple cloud services together.

<u>Technology</u>: React, React Native, Redux/Saga, react-query, react/testing-library, Node.js, GraphQL, Firebase Cloud Messaging, Branch.io, Buildkite, Web-driver IO, Appium, Cucumber, AWS (ECS, EKS, SQS, Device Farm, Cloudformation, S3, Lambda, and more), GCP (Storage, Composer, GKE, and more), Terraform, Kubernetes, ArgoWorkflow, ArgoCD, Go, Terraform, KubeCost, K6, Apache Spark, Hadoop, Airflow, Zookeeper, CircleCI, Pact Contract Testing, Cypress.

# Machine Learning & Software Engineer, OxygenAl Pte. Ltd. (Bangkok, Thailand) June 2018 - September 2019

Responsible for both developing AI models and implementing systems that make a full use of the models capabilities.

- Developed a data-collecting pipeline by coordinating multiple AWS services and show interesting data segmented by an AI on a dashboard in a mobile application for a retail store in Thailand, allowing the store to accurately identify their customer segments and increase rent in specific areas.
- Developed Mobile Application that can answer aggregated chat messages from Facebook & LINE in one place with AI. Allowing merchants to monitor their store on multiple platforms in one place.
- Developed a hotel-booking chatbot & call-centre bot using LINE and Twilio API to help the business better utilise their human resources, and fasten the booking process for their clients.

<u>Technology</u>: Tensorflow, Keras, Python, React/Typescript, Ionic/Angular, GraphQL, LINE Messaging API, Twilio.

#### **Technical Lead**, TEDxCharoenkrung. (Bangkok, Thailand)

June 2021 - December 2021 | tedxcharoenkrung.com

Volunteered to be a staff of a non-profit event called TEDxCharoenkrung, taking a role of a technical lead in the technology team. Responsible for building any tech-related systems for the event while collaborating with other teams to get the requirements and necessary information.

- Developed a responsive website with good SEO, and also design a way to allow people to register for and event, and also for future analytics purposes.
- Established a good work environment and ways of working within the team so that people with different backgrounds can efficiently work together.
- Planned the goals and milestones for the team and provided supports in any area which the team needed.

Technology: Next.js (React), Wordpress as CMS, Digital Ocean, Nuxt.js (Vue). Google API

#### Web & Machine Learning Developer, GISTDA. (Bangkok, Thailand)

August 2017 - May 2018

Collaborated with Geo-Informatics and Space Technology Agency (GISTDA) and helped them developed a machine learning model on their remote sensing data.

- Developed a web map application to visualise and perform semantic segmentation on satellite images, helping them reduce the time required from human to do the task, from months to just minutes of work. The semantic segmentation was done by a deep neural network model which was trained on their existing data.
- Published a research paper on a topic of using CNN to perform semantic segmentation on satellite images

<u>Technology</u>: React, Django, Leaflet, Keras, Tensorflow, Python

#### **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Engineering (Second class honours)**

Chulalongkorn University | GPAX 3.43/4.00 | May 2018

#### Side Projects (More on github.com/svnnynior)

React Visibility Tracking Hook Developed a React hook for tracking visibility status of web

elements in viewport, and published it as an npm package.

<u>The Greenvisible Cloak Web</u> Inspired by The Wizarding World of Harry Potter. It is a

website that can turn your blue or green cloak into an invisible

The Voice TH Data Visualisation A data D3.js visualisation of how The Voice TH's coaches pick

their team members.

Nerdy Project A 3D-renders of Marvel's Tesseract and Ready Player One's

EasterEgg. Written with THREE.js

#### **Publication**

<u>Semantic Segmentation on Medium-Resolution Satellite Images Using Deep Convolutional Networks with Remote Sensing Derived Indices</u> (2018)

#### Conference

Workshop Speaker @ PyCon Thailand, 2023

Facilitated the workshop with the topic "Hands-on GenAl via Python LangChain" to introduce the participants to the world of Generative Al and show them how they can easily use a framework called Langchain to develop a GenAl application. The session was well-received by the participants.

#### **Certificates / Courses**

- · AWS Certified Solution Architect Associate
- ACP Cloud Computing Certification (Alibaba Cloud)
- Three.js Journey Online Course (On-going)

## **Skills Summary**

Communication Languages Thai (Native), English (Proficient - IELTS Academic 7.5)

Programming Languages Javascript/Typescript, Python, Swift, Dart, Java, Scala

Web/Mobile React/React-Native, Next.js, Redux/Saga, React-Query,

GraphQL, Angular/Ionic, Vue.js, Svelte.js, Next.js, Gatsby.js,

Firebase, THREE.js, D3.js, branch.io, Flutter

Testing Tools Jest, Cypress, React/testing-library, msw, Cucumber, Appium,

Testcafe, Web-driver IO, K6

Databases MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Firebase Firestore, Redis

Data Engineering Apache Spark, Hadoop, Airflow, dbt, Beam, Fivetran, Databricks

Machine Learning Tersorflow, Keras, Langchain,

DevOps Tools Kubernetes, Docker, Terraform, CircleCl, Buildkite, Github Actions,

ArgoWorkflow, ArgoCD, GoCD,

Observability Datadog, Grafana, Prometheus, AWS Cloudwatch, Splunk

Cloud Provides Amazon Web Services (AWS), Google Cloud Platform (GCP),

Microsoft Azure, Alibaba Cloud